<locations>
	<entry>
		<title>1. Each &amp; Other - 6pm</title>
		<latitude>53.343650</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.277494</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Is it breaking the rules to have a 12 pubs with only 11 pubs on the route? Maybe. Nevertheless, a tradition that was started in our previous home now continues into our new HQ.<br><br>Entertainment for the evening will provided by E&O’s new second line, who will be having their inaugural rehearsal. Pizza and beers will be provided to alleviate the ordeal.<br><br>Leave the office, head around the corner and head for the Thomas House, our new local. ]]></hours>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<title>2. The Thomas House - 6.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.343082</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.276992</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Our new local has a fine selection of beers on tap, but don’t ask for a ‘lady pint’ as your request is likely to be met with disdain by the bar staff, who are not known for their polite demeanor.<br><br>Next we roll down towards the quays, arriving at the Brazen Head. Whoever gets caught out with the pudding costume at this point should be ashamed. You’ve only had two drinks! Stay on the ball!]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>3. The Brazen Head - 7pm</title>
		<latitude>53.345205</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.276423</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[The Brazen Head is officially Ireland's oldest pub, dating back to 1198. James Joyce, Brendan Behan and Jonathan Swift are former patrons. Apparently.<br><br>But now is not the time for reflecting on Ireland’s literary tradition. Back up the hill (who came up with this route?) to the Beer Market.]]></hours>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<title>4. The Beer Market - 7.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.343536</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.273326</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[The Beer Market is devoted to beer, as we are devoted to it.<br><br>Some fun facts<uL</ul><li>The Beer market is a beer-only bar, Ireland’s first</li><li>Up to 90% of the beer on tap at Beer Market is not available anywhere else in Ireland</li><li>Richey once proposed to the beer market, but was declined for having not enough hop and too much head.</li><ul><br>Now that we’ve experienced the joys of hipster beer-devotion, let’s continue towards a more spit and sawdust affair, the Lord Edward. Hop in through the side entrance and up the stairs to the lounge.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>5. Lord Edward - 8pm</title>
		<latitude>53.343280</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.270106</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Right lads, you should be well on the way to Christmas merriment at this stage, and what a time to enjoy my favourite pub on this year’s route.<br><br>The lounge upstairs is a fine spot for a gathering of hardy troupes such as ourselves. You’ll want to stay put on the cosy threadbare sofas and have a second Guinness, but stay focused! Laugh loudly at whoever has been lumped with the pudding costume and continue onto Darky Kelly’s.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>6. Darky Kelly's - 8.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.344134</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.269902</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Every pub on this year’s list went through a thorough selection process. Except for Darky Kelley’s, which had the benefit of being considered directly after the Chancery Inn, renowned as the ‘scaldiest’ pub in Dublin.<br><br>So that’s what happened. Next year, you citizens of democracy can elect new 12 pubs route planners. We’re here now, so drink quickly and prepare yourself for entry to TEMPLE BAR AT CHRISTMAS.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>7. Porterhouse Temple Bar - 9pm</title>
		<latitude>53.345278</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.267403</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[The half-way PINT! You’re on the home stretch now, which does NOT mean that you can go home, even if you’ve already paid for a yoga class at 10:30am, or your girlfriend will get pissy with you for coming home drunk, or you’ve lost your phone, wallet and keys. The next 6 pubs will be the making of you, and all the best stories of the night.<br><br>YOLO<br><br>Now we have a healthy riverside walk to Sin E to wake us up.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>8. Sin É - 9.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.345988</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.269534</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[If we were on one of Robert’s German pub crawls, the route would end here. Boo! A reduction to 8 pubs may work well in Germany, but sure you lot are only starting to heat up.<br><br>Sin E is an all round decent place to end up on your way home from after-work drinks on a Friday night. There might be live music in the back, but your best bet for a bit of entertainment is the smoking area at the front, where Rebecca should be in the midst of a passionate rant. Possibly about how she doesn’t want to go to Panti Bar. Stick the pudding costume on her and off we go!]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>9. Panti Bar - 10pm</title>
		<latitude>53.346577</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.267880</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Anyone who hasn’t heard of this place either lives under a rock or only reads newspaper articles written by John Waters.<br><br>Who’s wearing the pudding costume? Give them a hug. Give each and every other a hug!<br><br>Down the quays to the Grand Social next. Everyone look out for each other. We’re still on the Northside.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>10. The Grand Social - 10.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.346774</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.263246</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[So that was a nice little walk. Did you enjoy the little breather? Is everyone still together? No fights or stolen drinks? Good.<br><br>G’wan up to the smoking area upstairs. There’s a nice little photo booth in the corner. Richey you’re probably too young to remember, but a photo booth is something that people used to take photos before they had iPhones.<br><br>Next we’re tripping back across the river towards the Norseman in Temple Bar. The route has specifically been designed to pass through  Parliament Street, a mecca for lovers of alcohol-soaking, greasy stodge. Grab a kebab or a pizza slice to fortify yourself for rounds 11 and 12.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>11. The Norseman - 11pm</title>
		<latitude>53.345367</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.264765</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Nearly there! Our penultimate pint!<br><br>Anyone ever heard of the Norseman? No? Well someone put it on the list so here we are.<br><br>It was around pub 11 last year that Patrick regaled us with his ability to down a pint in one go. He absolutely loves attention and would be delighted to give us another show this year.<br><br>We should cling tightly to each other because right now we're likely to a) lose people and b) fall over.<br><br>Victory is nigh!]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>12. The Workman's Club - 11.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.345427</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.266491</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Ah, the Workman’s. The final resting place of manys a night that went from one drink to 12.<br><br>Everyone gather together for a photo of our glorious victory over all sensibility.<br><br>You’re fucked now, so you might as well stay out for a few more. Merry Christmas everyone!]]></hours>
	</entry>
</locations>