<locations>
	<entry>
		<title>1. Each &amp; Other - 6pm</title>
		<latitude>53.343650</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.277494</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Is it breaking the rules to have a 12 pubs with only 11 pubs on the route? Maybe. Nevertheless, it seems appropriate that we kick of this year's event at home in the Each&Other office. <br><br> We'll be cracking open our very own (and very palatable) E&O brew at 6pm sharp, joined by friends new and old. <br><br>Don't go to town on this beer though - it's somewhere around 6.5%. Stay in first gear for now – no one wants you trashing hotel rooms later.<br><br>Leave the office, head down Coppinger Row and see you at Grogan's. 
		
		]]></hours>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<title>2. The Thomas House - 6.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.343082</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.276992</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Grogan's has undergone a total renaissance over the past 15 or so years – without changing a single thing. It's gone from being the hangout of boozy failing writers, students and artists to being a catch-all pub for indigenous drinkers of all types. <br><br>An awesome daytime drinking spot, Grogan's is a groggy, black hole, sucking in Dubliners as they wander past. And they serve <i>amazing</i> toasties. <br><br>OK, OK, they’re just white bread, cheese and ham with some Coleman's on the side, but because you're usually plastered and starving when you order them, they've been elevated to legendary status by locals. <br><br>The indoor "art" exhibition changes regularly and is always awful. But that sort of adds to it. <br><br>Some people do not like this place. They are wrong. And probably also Bad People.<br><br>Next step, go *through* George's st arcade, turn left and go to Hogan's.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>3. The Brazen Head - 7pm</title>
		<latitude>53.345205</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.276423</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[A perfect spot for casual meet-ups, watching George's St traffic/people, and great for mid-week pints. Of course, this won’t be mid-week pints. Christmas time at this venerable and low-key institution can turn into a disastrous mess of ill-behaved office workers and general hooligan-ery. <br><br>We’ll only be on our third pint, so we should be among the better behaved. Also, Hogan's has some celebrity as one of only two bars that I've ever gotten kicked out of in Dublin.<br><br>Head accross the road to the Market Bar.]]></hours>
	</entry>
		<entry>
		<title>4. The Beer Market - 7.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.343536</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.273326</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Too uncomfortable when crowded, too cavernous when quiet, this mid Celtic tiger era tapas-boozer is still popular with the after-work crowd. While it’s probably not topping anyone’s Favourite Place in Dublin list, it’s a convenient stopping off point before we start onto George’s St, proper. The wooden shoe things on the wall aren't clogs, they are ‘lasts’. They are used by cobblers to do something. <br><br>(Are we really only on bar 4? Urgh.)<br><br>Turn left out of the Market Bar, and then right onto Drury St. P Mac's is straight ahead.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>5. Lord Edward - 8pm</title>
		<latitude>53.343280</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.270106</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[A casual low-key pan-atlantic quasi-european craft beer den. Or whatever. Regular readers of this list will know that last year we called this place 'try-hard' and reserved judgement on it. Well now after 12 months of bedding in, it's proving itself to be a vibrant and well-pitched addition to the after work scene. It suffers from the same pervasive stench of cheap pizza that floods its sister pubs Cassidy's and Blackbird, so hopefully you've already eaten.<br><br>Anyway, round five! Bottoms up. <br><br>Head out of P Mac's, go to Aungier St and walk a block or so South. the Swan is on your left.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>6. Darky Kelly's - 8.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.344134</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.269902</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[The Swan is a bit of a melting pot of a bar. Local residents from the notoriously dangerous Mercer St flats are frequently in attendance, as are delegates from Royal College of Surgeons conferences (who are arguably <i>more</i> dangerous), and DIT media students (the most dangerous of all). <br><br>One of only twelve remaining Victorian bars in Dublin, The Swan was used as a listening post for the rebels in the 1916 Rising, became a bastion for Irish ‘freedom fighters’ during the War of Independence and was occupied by anti-treaty forces during the Civl War. It’s steeped in history and violence. <br><br>The battling, anti-authoritarian spirt lives on in the area to this day (if the kids who kick footballs at my head on my way to work every morning are anything to go by).]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>7. Porterhouse Temple Bar - 9pm</title>
		<latitude>53.345278</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.267403</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Dublin bars used to have two functions – a place to run around trying to shift someone, or a place to moan about not being loved by anyone. Against the Grain is part of a new breed of businesses that are showing us that there’s more to pubs than misery and failure; there’s also great booze! <br><br>Serving a fine selection of craft beers from a vast array of taps (that keeps getting vaster, the success of this place has helped reenergise the Dublin drinking scene. <br><br>Having said that, it stinks of chips and vinegar before, during, and after its sub-par food service. <br><br>WARNING! Check the ABV before ordering anything that the bartender describes as ‘big’. <br><br>That is craft beer code for: ‘this beer will fuck with you’.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>8. Sin É - 9.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.345988</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.269534</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[The booths, over-bar mirror and layout of the downstairs of this place felt very New York and exciting when it opened up as the Modern Green Bar a million years ago. Solas faded a bit in relevance, but its still one of the few bars in town that makes a decent cocktail without making a gigantic song and dance about it. (Not that songs and dances aren't fine, sometimes). <br><br>Music and crowd vary from the tragic to the hip, depending on the night. I’m sure we’ll elevate the standard to the former. I mean latter. <br><br>Who knows what I mean. Also, it'd be wise if someone could keep track of Sheena in this bar. Drink up, we're two thirds of the way there.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>9. Panti Bar - 10pm</title>
		<latitude>53.346577</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.267880</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[A new addition to the list – as Whelan's proved a stumbling block last year (because we were all stumbling they wouldn't let us in. Ryan's is a venerable old journalist's hang out, particularlly popular with late working sub-editors finishing shifts on The Sun. It's also one of the few bars in the city centre where with a bit of a wink and a nod you'll be able to hang around for a lock in.<br><br> Keep whatever wits you have left about you. Last year one member of our party had to stare down a threatening local ruffian in a rather intense encounter. It's hard to look tough in a pudding costume.<br><br>Are you hitting the wall yet? <br><br>Please don't hit anything else.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>10. The Grand Social - 10.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.346774</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.263246</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[So that was a nice little walk. Did you enjoy the little breather? Is everyone still together? No fights or stolen drinks? Good. Alright so this is another change to our route from last year. Anseo hated us. How anyone could hate Geoffry dressed as a pudding … but whatever, We can take a message. So here we are at Cassidy's. This is a serviceble bar that still clings to Bill Clinton's visit in 1995. <br><br>We should cling tightly to each other because right now we're likely to a) lose people and b) fall over. ]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>11. The Norseman - 11pm</title>
		<latitude>53.345367</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.264765</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Nearly there! Our penultimate pint! <br><br>Apparently the Bleeding Horse got its name from the Battle of Rathmines in 1649, when a wounded horse fled from the clamor. Now its mostly an after work and sports bar crowd that lash in a few scoops, and either head off to party elsewhere or stick around and get smashed yelling at over paid men in shorts on TV. <br><br>It's big, but doesn’t really feel it because of all the nooks and crannies. There will, however, be no place to hide. <br><br>We, unlike the eponymous cowardly horse, will commit ourselves to the cause and proceed onward to the final reckoning.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>12. The Workman's Club - 11.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.345427</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.266491</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[How do you feel about ramshackle, tumbledown graffitied courtyards with big blue busses that serve pizza? Or a small sweaty black rooms with electro and dub step acts? Or pool tables and kids with tattoos and assorted Dublin creative types? <br>You love them? <br>Phew. <br>Because that's what this place is. Or was at least. The last couple of years have seen this place go mainstream. Cheap suits mingle with expensive haircuts freely. <br><br>If you want to end your 12 Pubs adventure in style, order a bottle of Buckfast. It's a more traditional Irish drink than Guinness will ever be.<br><br>Break out the sick bags, we’re done for another year! Happy Christmas! <br><br>Bleurgh…]]></hours>
	</entry>
</locations>