<locations>
	<entry>
		<title>1. Peters Pub - 6pm</title>
		<latitude>53.340936</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.263291</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[What's really nice about this great little spot is that, despite it's clean, modern interior, it's a pub with old school Dublin values; it's all class and no fuss. It boasts a good selection of wines (for a Dublin pub, at least) and it's <b>the</b> best place in town to get a hot whiskey*. And let’s not forget its proud iQ Content after work heritage. Where else would we kick off our epic journey?<br><br>
<i>*We do not recommend starting off the 12 pubs with a hot whiskey…</i>]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>2. P Mac's - 6.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.341148</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.264292</longitude>,
		<hours><![CDATA[A low key casual pan-atlantic, quasi-european craft beer den. Or whatever. Open only a wet week, it’s already constantly stuffed with of latest-thing seekers. It has a touch of the Cassidy’s or Westmoreland St about it – the bar is crammed full of random crap to make it look like it’s been there for decades. (Yes, brand new inflatable R2D2, you are the warning sign of the try-hard). I also suspect that they’ve pre-melted a lot of candles to create the candle drippy atmosphere. Anyway, round two! Bottoms up.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>3. Grogan's - 7pm</title>
		<latitude>53.342211</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.262531</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Grogan's has undergone a total renaissance over the past 15 or so years. Without changing a single thing, it's gone from being the hangout of boozy failing writers, students and artists to being a catch-all pub for every type of indigenous drinker. An awesome daytime drinking spot, Grogan's is like a boozy, black hole, sucking in Dubliners as they wander past. And they serve amazing toasties. OK, OK, they’re just white bread, cheese and ham with some Coleman's on the side, but you're usually plastered and starving when you order them they've been elevated to legendary status by locals. The indoor art exhibition changes regularly and is always awful. But that sort of adds to it. Some people do not like this place. They are wrong. And probably also Bad People.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>4. Market Bar - 7.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.342039</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.264042</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Too uncomfortable when crowded, too cavernous when quiet, this mid-Celtic tiger era tapas-boozer is still popular with the after-work crowd. While it’s probably not topping anyone’s Favourite Place in Dublin list, it’s a convenient stopping off point before we start onto George’s St., proper. The wooden ‘shoes’ things on the wall are called ‘lasts’. They are used by cobblers to do something. (Are we really only on bar 4? Urgh.)]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>5. Hogans - 8pm</title>
		<latitude>53.341992</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.2645969</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[A perfect spot for casual meet-ups and watching George's St traffic/people watching and great for mid-week pints. Of course, this won’t be mid-week pints. Christmas time at this normally venerable and low-key institution can turn into a disastrous mess of ill-behaved office workers and general hooligan-ery. But since we’ll be on our fifth pint, we should fit right in.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>6. The Swan Bar - 8.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.33965</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.2657167</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[The Swan is a bit of a melting pot of a bar. Local residents from the notoriously dangerous Mercer St flats are frequently in attendance, as are delegates from Royal College of Surgeons conferences (who are arguably <i>more</i> dangerous), and DIT media students (the most dangerous of all). One of only twelve remaining Victorian bars in Dublin, the Swan was used as a listening post for the rebels in the 1916 Rising, became a bastion for Irish ‘freedom fighters’ during the War of Independence and was occupied by anti-treaty forces during the Civl War. It’s steeped in history and violence. The battling anti-authoritarian spirt lives on in the area (if the kids who kick footballs at my head on my way to work every morning are anything to go by).]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>7. Against the Grain - 9pm</title>
		<latitude>53.337021</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.2656021</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Dublin bars used to have two functions – a place to run around trying to shift someone, or a place to moan about not being loved by anyone. Against the Grain is part of a new breed of pubs that are showing us that there’s more to pubs than misery and failure; there’s also great booze! <br>Serving a fine selection of craft beers from a vast array of taps, the success of this place has helped reenergise the Dublin drinking scene. Although, it stinks of chips and vinegar during and after its sub par food service. <br>WARNING! Check the ABV before ordering anything that the bartender describes as ‘sessionable’. That is code for : ‘this is a beer for grown ups’.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>8. Solas - 9.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.336977</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.2656537</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[The booths, over-bar mirros and layout of the downstairs of this place felt very New York and exciting when it opened up as the Modern Green Bar a million years ago. It’s faded a bit in relevance, but its still one of the few bars in town that makes a decent cocktail without making a gigantic song and dance about it. (Not that songs and dances aren't fine, sometimes). Music and crowd vary from the tragic to the hip, depending on the night. I’m sure we’ll elevate the standard to the former. I mean latter. Who knows what I mean. Drink up, we're two thirds of the way there.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>9. Whelan's - 10pm</title>
		<latitude>53.336576</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.265646</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA["Over the years Whelan’s has expanded out in all directions, including up. It now has four bar areas – the venue, the main bar, the upstairs, and another bit that looks like a living room.  It can get confusing for people on pub crawls. If you get lost just ask for the MAIN BAR from a 20-year old girl with a ripped Sonic Youth T shirt (there’ll be one near by, don’t worry). Are you hitting the wall yet?]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>10. Anseo - 10.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.335279</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.265132</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[One of the best bars in the city. Dark – very dark in fact – with gig posters on the wall, book shelves filled with dog eared paperbacks, great soul, rock n'roll and hip-hop tunes played slightly too loudly, a solid selection of decent brews and top bar staff. It’s *really* hard not to use the word dive, so I'm just going to fire it out there. This bar is a dive. A perfect, glorious, wonderful, rough and tumble dive. And with all the things that go with it: great banter, interesting graffiti in the toilet, lots of shadowy corners and everyone who goes there looks like someone that you ought to know. It’ll be crammed on Friday. But that’s OK, the crush of the crowd will help you not fall over.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>11. The Bleeding Horse - 11pm</title>
		<latitude>53.333529</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.264981</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[Nearly there! Our penultimate pint! Apparently the Bleeding Horse got its name from the Battle of Rathmines in 1649, when a wounded horse fled from the clamor. Now its mostly an after work and sports bar crowd that lash in a few scoops and either head on to party elsewhere or stick around and get smashed. It's big, but doesn’t really feel it because of all the nooks and crannies. There will, however, be no place to hide. We, unlike the eponymous horse will commit ourselves to the cause and proceed onward to the final reckoning.]]></hours>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<title>12. The Bernard Shaw - 11.30pm</title>
		<latitude>53.331715</latitude>
		<longitude>-6.264575</longitude>
		<hours><![CDATA[How do you feel about ramshackle, tumbledown graffitied courtyards with big blue busses that serve pizza? Or a small sweaty black rooms with electro and dub step acts? Or pool tables and kids with tattoos and a sprinkling of Dublin creative types? You love them? Phew. Because that's what this place is.<br>If you want to end your 12 Pubs adventure in style, order a bottle of Buckfast. It's a more traditional Irish drink than Guinness will ever be.<br>Break out the sick bags, we’re done for another year!]]></hours>
	</entry>
</locations>